Privacy Policy
==============

**Privacy Policy – Revised November 2018**

1. **Introduction**

This Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") describes how the website ("QuestionCove") collects, uses and discloses information from and about visitors and users of QuestionCove, including unregistered visitors ("Visitors"), registered user ("Members") and unregistered guests ("Guests"), as each category is further described in the Terms of Use, and what choices Members, Guests and Visitors each have regarding the collection and use of such information. This Privacy Policy also explains procedures for the security and protection of the information collected and how you can access and update your information.

By registering with the QuestionCove website or by using any of the QuestionCove products or services as a Member or Guest, or by accessing the website as a Visitor, you agree to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy, including QuestionCove’s policies with respect to the collection, use, and disclosure of personal and non-personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

2. **Information Collected**

QuestionCove collects and stores certain personally identifiable information about you when you provide it to us during registration (or when you update your account information), when you use or subscribe to QuestionCove’s products and services, including when you respond to QuestionCove’s surveys or submit content or materials to QuestionCove, or when you otherwise communicate with QuestionCove, such as through emails. The type of personally identifiable information collected may include your name, address, email address, telephone number, credit card information, school, demographic information, and other personal information, depending upon the particular QuestionCove product or service, the information requested and provided and the category of user.

QuestionCove also collects and stores certain non-personally identifiable information about you when you visit and use the Web Site or otherwise interact with QuestionCove, including using QuestionCove's products and services, submitting content or materials to QuestionCove and responding to surveys and email communications. The type of non-personal information collected may include your computer and internet connection information, including your IP address, operating system, and usage history of the website and its web pages.

This non-personal information may be gathered by using "cookies" and/or "clear GIF" (Graphical Interchange Format) technologies, as well as login file information. "Cookies" are small data files with a unique identifier that we transfer to your computer's hard drive or web browser and that collect and store data about your visit to the website. This allows our systems to identify you when you return to the website and to analyze your website usage. "GIFs" are small graphic files with a unique identifier contained in our website that we use to track website traffic. This allows us to monitor and improve the performance of the website and the related services offered and to collect and use the information as described in this Privacy Policy. This non-personally identifiable information will be treated in the same fashion, and in aggregate to, all information provided by a Member, Guest or Visitor.

3. **Use of Information**

QuestionCove uses your personal and non-personal information in order to improve and personalize your use of the website and its related products and services, including the tracking and monitoring of traffic on the website to enhance the performance of the website.

QuestionCove does not share your personal information with third parties, except to the extent necessary to process transactions with you (for example, credit card processing companies, or in cases that include a third-party partner). However, QuestionCove may disclose any such information pursuant to law, including subpoena, warrants or other orders; in order to enforce the Terms of Use or other website policies and rules with respect to a particular QuestionCove product or service including reporting suspected cheating or intellectual property rights violations to your academic institution or others who have a need to know of such activity, or any other related agreements between you and QuestionCove; or as otherwise may be required to protect the rights of QuestionCove, its directors, officers, representatives and agents, or its Members, Guests or Visitors.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here ([optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/)).

Except as described above, QuestionCove will not disclose any personal information about you to third parties without your permission.

We may share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our partners. This information does not identify individual users.

As a user or guest, you may access and update your personal information as described in the Terms of Use, however, information originally submitted to QuestionCove by you may be retained by QuestionCove for technical, legal or other reasons.

4. **General Limitations**

This Privacy Policy is part of the Terms of Use. QuestionCove may revise or amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, and it is your responsibility to regularly review this Privacy Policy for any changes to it. If you have any questions or concerns about privacy at QuestionCove or about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at [contact@questioncove.com](mailto:contact@questioncove.com).

QuestionCove implements reasonable steps to maintain the privacy and security of your information against unauthorized access consistent with industry standards, however, as with all online transactions, "hackers" or other third parties may intercept and misuse your personal information, including during transmission to and from the website or related services.

The website and its related products and services are not intended for use by children under 13 years of age and children under 13 may not submit personal information to QuestionCove. QuestionCove will not knowingly collect or use personal information of anyone under 13 years of age, and if QuestionCove is informed or determines that any such information has been submitted, it will be deleted, unless a parent or guardian authorizes use of the service.

**I am over 13 years of age, and agree to the Terms of Use and understand the Privacy Policy.**
